fcagroup.com 2012-03-18

# Privacy Policy - Reppa Flags and Souvenirs

**Reppa Flags & Souvenirs Online Privacy Policy**

Reppa Flags & Souvenirs is committed to respecting the privacy rights of our website visitors. How we collect, protect and use information we receive from website visitors is described in the following policy.

By using our website, you signify that you agree with the current terms of the Privacy Policy as posted in this area of the site and to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as detailed in this policy. If you do not agree with any of the terms of this Policy, please do not use our site.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you make a purchase on the Reppa Flags & Souvenirs web site.

When making a purchase on our web site we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, country, postal code and credit card information or other information (collectively your "personally identifiable information").

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them. We also receive and store click-stream data and other information about visits to our websites, which may be combined with other data. This information is used to analyze and improve the website experience for all of our users.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you make a purchase on the web site in the following ways:

• To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
• To learn about site visitors and customers and to tailor specific features, promotions, or other notifications to you.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and we use best efforts to ensure that it is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use "cookies"?**

Yes. Cookies are pieces of information that a site sends to your computer while you are viewing the site. Cookies work in combination with content within the site itself to capture and remember information. For instance, cookies are used to track your activity and understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity. This enables us to provide you with services or to improve your site experience. We also use cookies to provide us with aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third party service providers to assist us in serving cookies, however, they are not permitted to use the information collected except to help Reppa Flags & Souvenirs conduct and improve its business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient -- like the features mentioned above -- and some of our services will not function properly.

**Do we disclose the information we collect from our visitors to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Reppa Flags & Souvenirs. It also does not include our website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting Reppa Flags & Souvenirs business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

**A Special Note to Parents**

We realize that children may visit our site, and we therefore encourage children to consult with their parents before submitting any information to any website, including ours. We encourage parents to supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other personal information online without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please consult the Privacy and Ethics page of the Canadian Marketing Association website at www.the-cma.org

**Third-Party Links**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

**Changes to Our Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. We encourage you to visit this page frequently so that you are aware of our current policy.

**Questions and Feedback**

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.

This site is operated by Reppa Flags & Souvenirs and the site's servers are housed in Canada. Please note, that when you enter any sub-sites accessible through www.fcagroup.com, such sub-sites may be operated by different entities with their own privacy policies specific to those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those sites.

**NOTICE OF COPYRIGHT**

The Reppa Flags & Souvenirs web site may contain information which is copyrighted by others. No part of the web site may be reproduced in any form without the prior written permission of the copyright holder.
